Galley Channel, go-go!
Yes, today will be the second round of Quote Cutting. The rules are tournament system. This time.
The situation is that you fight one on one, and the people who have risen to the top will fight each other. So you fight within one minute at the end.
Yes, that's right. How is it? How long has it been? It's been quite a while.
Less than two years.
Has it been that long? Yes, it has.
No, I think I'd like to see it again. I can't do that warp. It's been over two years. It's impossible.
I'm going to break it. So you and Kida will start with a showdown?
Really? No way.
You want to go at it alone first? Wouldn't it be better to do it alone?
I guess so. If we lose, it's over.
We'll see each other in the final battle. Okay.
Oh, hot. Hot.
Well, let's go hit it.
Trying to decide hot. Let's go right away.
Start the video!
This time we are wearing Teeholic's costumes.
In the first round, it's a showdown between Capei and Kida-chan.
If there is a first one, Kida-chan will start.
Yes, that's right. I have to go to the toa in the final round,
I can't lose here,
I wonder if you can afford to lose to Misakii.
I'm really weak.
I'm weak in this kind of thing,
There are a lot of trials to meet in comic books,
I was hoping it would be one of them.
I don't want to be the one to lose.
But I know that everyone might be expecting me to win,
I will win as much as I can.
Are you ready?
Let's go!
One minute.
One shake.
Face.
Yay!
That's what I've been saying outside.
So, how was it?
But, Kimura-san won.
I can tell he's around here somewhere,
But I was a bit hesitant because I thought it was a one-time thing.
But it was great that he was able to make that decision,
Please look at the commentary today,
Thank you very much for coming to Toa-chan.
Congratulations.
See you again.
And now, the second game is Minami versus Toyoda.
What was that? How are you feeling about it?
Those shoes are a little noisy.
I'll try my best not to make a sound, based on what I remember from earlier.
I'm not so sure about this.
I'll do my best.
Then, please spin the wheel.
Wow, wow, wow.
That's gross.
I really don't like it.
Okay, stop.
Here we go.
I don't know if I can do this.
Do you think it's okay?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I can't get a rash.
I just got dumped.
Oh my god, this girl.
I'm going to dump both of them and reset it once.
Turn?
I don't like spinning.
It's going to be a minute.
Thank you for watching.
Pow!
Wow!
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Oh, thank God!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
It felt like Yuko was doing a lot of stabbing.
Minami didn't notice anything the whole time.
Okay, in the middle.Okay, so in the middle.
In the middle.
That's it.
How was that?
That's good.
Good.
Yuko lately.
Really?
No, but not at all.
All that clinking.
It feels so far away.
It feels closer.
I don't know.
On the contrary...
Pow!
That was beautiful!
The third match will be between Youka and Towa.
Let's hear what you have to say. Well, I won last time, so I'll do my best to continue that.
I'd like to continue to do my best. I'm really nervous because my opponent was the champion last time.
I'm really nervous, but I'm not going to let her practice.
So I'm going to drop him here.
Okay, then. Please spin me around.
I'm in position.
Here we go.
What? That was fast.
We're not done. We're not done.
One at a time.
I just swung it, didn't I?
Oh, my God!
Ew! That's scary!
It hurts a little bit!
Scary!
I can see something!
I don't know if I saw it.
No!
Ryoka was looking at me.
But he took a step forward and cut himself.
That's great!
I thought it was too far.
It was too close for Ryoka.
He made the cut so late.
You did it!
Thank you so much!
And the winner is Tomachan.
Good job!
And now, for the fourth pair, we have Momoko and Clear.
How are you doing, Momo?
Well, she's in heels today.
I'm a little worried.
But I'll do my best.
Okay.
I don't feel like I can win either.
But I'll give it my best.
I'll do my best.
You're off to a good start.
Good night.
What do you guys look like?
Let us know in the comments section!
See you next time!
Bye bye!
Oh, no.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Why didn't you run away at the end? Oh, God.
Ha-ha-ha.
Why did you give it to me?
I got chased by some criminal.
Like at the end.
I can't move from the wall.
Ahh...
That was fast. I'll clear it.
But you're cute. The way you swing.
I thought it wouldn't hurt if it got cold.
If you couldn't move at the end, did you give up?
No, I thought it was the writer who didn't move.
Oh, I wouldn't do that.
But in the end, I lost.
Next time, you should move forward.You should move forward for the next one.
Ha ha ha.
Now, that was today's victory.
Applause.
Okay, now for the second round.
How about you, Kira-san, since we're talking about Kira versus Yuzu.
I was watching Yuzu earlier, and he looked strong, so I'll give it a shot.
I see. How about Yuzu?
I'm pretty chicken, and Kira is pretty strong, so I'm scared of her.
I see.
Let's see if she's like Kira of your dreams.
Cheer for me. I'll be waiting.
Here we go! Start!
Start!
We both saw it, didn't we?
Oh, we saw it.
Both of you.
I saw it.
I saw both of you.
I saw them both.
Aah!
Oh!
You're so strong!
Oh, no!
Aah!
Well, I'm still going.
You're still good.
Sorry.
It's too close.
I'll have Riku-chan turn it.
Too strong.
Thank you for watching.
Something fell.
It fell.
It fell so hard.
Not so bad, huh?
Okay, here we go.
All right, start.
He's down.
Wow.
Aaaaah! Alas, my Lord!
Aaaaah! I've been decapitated!
No! Oh no!
That's great, Ei-chan!
But it's okay to have each other!
Yes! We have all the right spots!
Kira's coming so fast, Yuuchan's all over the place!
Yuuchan walked a lot just now!
Kira was walking a lot too!
But it was a great competition, wasn't it?
Sorry it took so long!
That's amazing! Embarrassing!
Good luck!
Good luck! Good luck!
Round 3 is Momoka and Towa's wine showdown!
How are you doing, Momoka?
I'll do my best not to hurt you!
That's right!
If you don't try, you won't get hurt!
How about you, Mr. Towa?
Well, if we win this, is it the last game?
Yes!
So I'll do my best!
Yes, sir!
Okay, I'll turn it around!
Here we go!
Hello!
Today, I'm going to make a watermelon.
Watermelons are many kinds of watermelons.
Watermelons are many kinds of watermelons.Watermelons come in many varieties.
Okay, here we go.
All right, let's start!
Yes, go, go, go!
All right, let's go!
Start, start, start!
Yeah, start!
boom!
Aah!
Caw!!!!
I can't believe how bad the live ones were.
Did I hit it?
I hit it!
Yes!
Thank you so much for your hard work.
You won the study.
Come on!
Oh, my gosh!
Let's go to the final round, shall we?
The final is in Odawara!
You did it!
That's too much!
So, the final will be Yuzuha vs.
Let's hear Yuzuha's enthusiasm.
Well, I didn't expect to face Toa,
Well, I'll do my best anyway.
Okay, what about Toa?
Well, I was the first place last time,
I would like to be number one here.
I see.
Good luck with your goal of becoming a leper.
Okay.
Okay, let's go around.
Here we go. Okay, let's start!
Oh, wow!
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
And so it goes.
The winner is Yuka!
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
That was amazing!
It went down, didn't it?
I did it in a hurry.
I had to get my foot out.
That's why you touched me so suddenly.
I see.
Congratulations!
That was pretty much a one-shot deal.
Amazing.
We won!
I feel so good.
That's great.
It feels so good!
Congratulations!
Good game! Good game!
It feels really good.
It's very vocal.
I only got to see one of them.
It's worth watching.
Thank you for watching.
If you liked today's video, please click the Good Button
Good Button
Please leave a comment, subscribe to the channel, and leave a comment!
Bye-bye!